The second quest…
THE SECOND QUEST IS REVEALED
is Baengnokdam Crater Lake
at Hallasan Mountain.
Goodbye!
I somewhat expected it, but…
THE HIGHEST MOUNTAIN IN KOREA
HALLASAN, 1,950 M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
President Tar,
could you brief us on the schedule?
HE PLANNED
FOR THEIR HALLASAN CLIMB
I need to see the schedule.
DESCEND CLUB'S FIRST EXPEDITION
TO JEJU ISLAND
GIMPO INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
JEJU INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
ARRIVAL AT JEJU INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
Hey, I'll go withdraw money for the fee…
I mean, the fine.
TAEBAEKSAN
DESCEND CLUB RULES
NEGATIVE COMMENT: 300,000-WON FINE
I really can't do this show.
Jung-won? Jung-won.
INCURS 300,000-WON FINE
-Can you do this show?
-Of course.
It's 300,000 won, right?
MINUS 300,000 WON
STRENGTHS: ADMIT MISTAKES
AND ENGAGES IN SELF-REFLECTION FAST
First off, I'll pay the fine.
-President Tar, here's the fine.
-The fine.
-I should count to make sure, right?
-You should.
But the manager manages our money.
-Right, give it back.
-Okay.
I counted it correctly.
President Tar, where to now?
-To rent a car.
-Yes.
LET'S GO RENT A CAR FIRST
DOMESTIC ARRIVALS
The weather's okay.
The weather's so nice.
JEJU ISLAND
CURRENTLY 6.4°C
The weather's good.
I think we could hike in hoodies.
Yeah.
-We won't need padded jackets.
-Right.
Right, we won't.
Doesn't it feel like spring?
IT'S FEBRUARY
BUT IT FEELS LIKE SPRING IN JEJU
Why is the weather so nice?
It's so good.
This is insane.
THE JEJU EXPEDITION IS OFF TO A GOOD START
We can see
the Hallasan summit from here.
-What?
-Where?
We can see it so clearly.
Is that Hallasan?
The air must be really clear.
THANKS TO CLEAR WEATHER
HALLASAN IS VISIBLE FROM EVERYWHERE
Who's going to drive?
I'll do it today,
since you did it last time.
No, it's all right.
Chae-min is driving?
Area C11 is here.
LCM AKA LEE CHAE-MIN IS DRIVING TODAY
Should we go eat that thing first?
-Mulhoe, right?
-Yes.
Here we go.
ABALONE RESTAURANT
JEJU INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
To avoid confusion this time,
I'll pay for everything
and tell you the amount later.
Sure, sounds great.
WE ALWAYS SPLIT THE BILL EVENLY
Let's try it.
-"Abalone restaurant."
-This will be good.
Gosh, there are so many good dishes.
They're all abalone dishes. Nice.
So many delicious dishes.
IT HAS EVERY ABALONE DISH
-We didn't get to eat abalone in Gangwon.
-Right.
So while looking for restaurants,
I thought we should have it
as soon as we get to Jeju.
Should we just order a full spread?
Sure.
WITH ABALONE CAUGHT BY HAENYEO
A TABLE FULL OF ABALONE DISHES
TO GIVE THEM ENERGY FOR HIKING
ABALONE MULHOE
We should use wooden chopsticks for this.
ABALONE SASHIMI
GRILLED ABALONE
ABALONE STEW
ABALONE PORRIDGE
OCTOPUS, SEA PINEAPPLE, SEA CUCUMBER
TILEFISH, SEA URCHIN SOUP
It's an abalone feast.
Gosh, this is amazing.
-Bon appétit.
-Thank you for the food.
-Gosh.
CHEWY ABALONE SASHIMI FIRST
It's good.
DOWOON TRIES MULHOE FIRST
-Thank you for the food.
-Thank you.
Mulhoe is so fresh.
-The rice has beans too.
-I'll try butter-grilled one.
-Is it good?
-It melts in your mouth.
We're practically swimming
in a sea of abalone.
SAVORING THE SEA URCHIN AND SEAWEED SOUP
-Should we have ordered one more soup?
-No.
-We can just eat a variety of dishes.
-Right.
HE WANTS MORE SOUP
THEY TRY THE OCTOPUS
AND TURBAN SNAIL SKEWERS TOO
I think they're octopus
and turban snail skewers.
THE FUN OF PICKING WHAT THEY WANT
-The tilefish is really good.
-Yeah.
How are abalone and hiking related?
Related?
Delicious…
-Delicious?
-Delicious…
Hiking is delicious?
ABALONE PORRIDGE TO FINISH THE MEAL
HOW HIKING AND ABALONE ARE RELATED
ACCORDING TO CAR, THE GARDEN'S CHATGPT
1. TAURINE, A KEY TO RECOVERY FROM FATIGUE
2. HIGH IN PROTEIN AND LOW IN FAT
TO PREVENT MUSCLE LOSS
This is good.
The porridge's really good.
3. REPLENISHES MINERALS AND ELECTROLYTES
4. ARGININE TO IMPROVE BLOOD FLOW
-Tarzzan found a good restaurant.
-Right.
I'm actually a pretty picky eater.
But everything…
-Were you satisfied?
-I was.
Ma'am, could we get the check please?
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-I'll just pay for it with my fine, okay?
Sure.
It's 235,000 won.
I'll pay in cash.
Thank you.
I haven't seen anyone
pay with cash in a while.
Thank you for the food.
AFTER ENJOYING AN ABALONE FEAST
ABALONE RESTAURANT
HAMDEOK BEACH
Isn't it beautiful?
THEY ARRIVE AT A BEACHFRONT CAFE
Let's take a picture.
PHOTO TIME ON TERRACE
I already set the dial.
What about the flash?
One, two, three.
Let me take yours.
All right. One, two, three.
The water is so clear.
Tell me about it.
I feel like I'm on vacation.
The color looks amazing.
THE REFRESHING SCENERY
MAKES IT FEEL LIKE VACATION
-Let's take a picture.
-I brought a film camera.
Really? You brought it?
Yeah, just in case.
HE BROUGHT IT SINCE IT'S JEJU
Should we do a fist pump? The hiking pose?
One, two, three.
Can we take photo booth pictures?
-Sounds great.
-Sounds good.
That's perfect
for capturing this nice moment.
Hurry.
I want to put the photo on my fridge.
Now, we're all in it.
Look how close we've become.
Car-the, try smiling cheerfully.
GRINNING
-I'm going to put it on my fridge.
-Okay.
-The original?
-Yes, the original.
-This will be a nice memory.
-Right, a fond memory.
Definitely.
Chae-min, you're so handsome.
BUILDING TEAMWORK AND MAKING MEMORIES
It came out well.
MINISTER OF TRANSPORT RETURNS TO HIS POST
I got to take pictures with celebrities.
I should be the one saying that.
Where are we going?
Big Ball Land.
NEXT IS A MYSTERIOUS ACTIVITY
PRESIDENT TAR DISCOVERED
HAMDEOK BEACH
BIG BALL LAND
I wish the show
was about going on a trip to Jeju.
We were busy chatting
that we came in no time.
THEY ARRIVE AT THE ACTIVITY
The balls are huge.
-They roll down side by side.
-Is that it?
Don't tell me we have to walk there.
There's no chairlift.
ON A HIGH HILL
GIANT ORBS
TWO PEOPLE CAN RIDE IN EACH BALL
RECREATIONAL SPORT
OF ROLLING DOWN A 300-METER SLOPE
IN GIANT ORBS
TO PREPARE FOR HIKING HALLASAN
PRESIDENT TAR PREPARED THIS ACTIVITY
TO IMPROVE THEIR SENSE OF BALANCE
-Tarzzan, ride with me.
-Okay.
And Car-the should ride with Dowoon
so the weights match.
And over there…
Other shows have filmed here,
and the scenes look almost the same.
Can we avoid filming that scene?
SIGNS OF OTHER SHOWS THAT CAME BY
We should avoid scenes like these.
Don't put in subtitles like this as well.
Don't put subtitles at all.
"An exhausted beetle"!
Hello.
I feel like those scenes will happen.
I don't like it.
Just like those classic variety shows.
ACTIVITY-SPECIFIC FILMING EQUIPMENT
Like those classic weekend variety shows
to entertain viewers.
Is this right?
PUTS IT RIGHT ON
This is what's funny.
You don't have to
try too hard to be funny.
SPREADING LAUGHTER
CHAE-MIN AND TARZZAN DEPART FIRST
Geez. Who would've thought
we'd ride these?
-I've never done this before.
-Me neither.
I didn't expect this.
You can get out here.
-Okay.
-Okay. Thank you.
CHAE-MIN AND TARZZAN
ARRIVE AT THE STARTING POINT
Are you ready?
I am.
Hold on. This looks…
We'll be rolling for a while.
THEY WILL ROLL DOWN THIS WAY
The orbs are bigger than expected.
Watch your head.
GET IN
What is this?
LOSING THEIR SENSE OF BALANCE
-Come on, stay still.
-What's wrong?
-You are…
-You do it first.
ALL SET
Dowoon, don't exaggerate your reactions.
-I hate that.
-I never do that.
Rolling down is honestly not that fun.
"Gosh, it must be hard for them."
Don't do that.
This is 2026.
5 SECONDS BEFORE RELEASE
NERVOUS
They're screaming like hell.
TARZZAN, CHAE-MIN
CHAOS INSIDE THE ORB
LOOKS CALM ON THE OUTSIDE
Just film this. It's funny.
It's a bit violent.
I can't see!
Hey, I can't see anything!
BEING MERCILESSLY TURNED INSIDE OUT
I can't see!
ABOUT TO VOMIT THE ABALONE HE ATE
I feel like throwing up.
Hold on. Where are we?
WHERE? YOU'RE AT THE END
DIZZY
You can unstrap and get out.
You go first.
I'm dizzy.
I'll get out. Be careful.
STAGGERING
Hi.
GETTING OUT IS ALSO NOT EASY
Gosh.
I feel sick.
Hey, let's…
-It's so fun!
-Hey, it's so fun!
You have to do this.
Seriously!
People sound like that when they lie.
I think we picked the wrong one.
Seriously.
Hey.
Was it fun?
You become so much closer.
Really, it's fun.
VERY WORRIED
-We got a lot closer.
-Really.
I think we can ride that later
when we descend the mountain.
Isn't that a good idea?
We can rent them for the day.
It'll take an hour less to descend.
I think it'd only take 15 minutes
to come down in those.
Then, let's decide after you try it.
-I'll go see how it feels.
-Okay.
-Good luck.
Sir, is this really popular?
CAR, THE GARDEN AND DOWOON
I'm so curious to see how they'll be
when they come down.
-The heavier one will go to the right.
-That's me.
-Get in?
-Yes.
And take off your shoes.
Take off your shoes.
To the person on the right,
how much do you weigh?
Almost 100 kg.
It's 95 kg.
It must be accurate.
How about the other?
I'm 60… I'm 65 kg.
Strap in your ankles first.
ABOUT 160 KG IN TOTAL
CAR, THE GARDEN AND DOWOON ARE READY
We'll let the air out a bit more.
Since you're heavy, it's dangerous.
We'll deflate it more
so it goes slower.
HISSING
I'm scared. I'm a bit nervous.
Hey, this is…
CACKLING
Rolling down is honestly not that fun.
SO FUN
DOWOON'S SELF-CAM TURNED OFF
WHILE ROLLING DOWN
EVEN WITH LESS AIR, IT'S ROLLING FAST
What is this?
-It looks really pathetic from here.
-So pathetic.
What is this?
IT LOOKS FUNNY FROM AFAR
It's so pitiful.
What on earth is this?
AND IT LOOKS FUNNIER UP CLOSE
I told you we shouldn't have done this!
They're saying something.
I told you we shouldn't do this!
What on earth is this?
CAN'T TELL
IF THEY'RE LAUGHING OR SCREAMING
AN EXHAUSTED BEETLE
Okay, you've arrived.
You can take both hands off.
COMPLETELY WORN OUT
How was it?
I hated it.
I'm never doing it again.
-I'm never doing it again.
-I hated it so much.
I'm the one who suggested this.
I'm in big trouble now.
-I should run away.
-Run.
I need to run away.
THANKS TO PRESIDENT TAR,
THEIR SENSE OF BALANCE IMPROVED
It was something
I'd never experienced before.
That's what I felt too.
That was such a strange…
It was a strange feeling.
-You may get out.
-What on earth was that?
The really scary thing was…
Before we got in the ball,
he was like, "Who's heavier?"
"How much do you weigh?"
"I weigh 90--"
-"It must be accurate."
-We got the same.
I mean, that was so sudden and scary.
"Tell me the exact number!"
Why are you crying?
"We need to deflate it."
He's crying.
"You can't roll down like this."
-You felt sick, right?
-He said to me,
"I told you I didn't want to do it!"
We're finally going home.
Seriously, in those big orbs…
Didn't you feel like throwing up?
Just as you said,
we came down so pathetically.
You can't help it. You're strapped in.
It was so bouncy.
I feel so drained too.
MOVING TO BASE CAMP
BIG BALL LAND
BASE CAMP
After all that fun,
it's still 3:30 p.m.
We must have arrived in Jeju really early.
A LAZY AFTERNOON IN JEJU
It's so cloudy only around Hallasan.
-Where's Hallasan?
-Is that it?
That's Hallasan? No way.
Over there. Way in the distance.
Not this one, right?
No, the one in the distance.
IT'S BECOME CLOUDY AROUND HALLASAN
THE WEATHER AROUND BAENGNOKDAM
CHANGES RAPIDLY
WILL THEY BE ABLE TO SEE
BAENGNOKDAM TOMORROW?
I bet it'll be cold in the morning.
Probably so.
I bet it'll be very windy.
But compared to the mountains we've hiked,
I think it will be much warmer.
-It's like a whole town.
-This kind of vibe?
There are even vans.
THEY ARRIVE AT BASE CAMP
There are even limousines here.
Gosh, limousines.
Gosh, it looks amazing.
Will we get breakfast too?
WITH HALLASAN BEHIND THEM IN THE DISTANCE
THEIR JEJU ISLAND BASE CAMP
I suddenly feel excited.
ENTERING IN A GOOD MOOD
LOBBY
There's no elevator?
Is this training for hiking?
What is this place? There are even drums.
Dowoon, this is a place for you.
I know. Should we play
"My Whole World," Jung-won?
This will be so fun!
I want to play music together.
LIVING ROOM
KITCHEN
THERE'S EVEN A SECOND FLOOR
DESCEND CLUB CHECKS IN
The living room is mine.
DOWOON TAKES THE LIVING ROOM AGAIN
Shouldn't we play some live music here?
It's all set up.
GOES AS IF DRAWN TO THE DRUMS
This is nice.
SITS DOWN WITH FAMILIAR EASE
Dowoon's on the drums.
AUTOMATICALLY PRODUCES A BEAT
THIS IS THE MINISTER OF TRANSPORT'S
REAL JOB
He's already started playing the drums.
THE END
Why did you stop?
Hey, play something for us.
Play something without copyright issues.
Without copyright issues?
THE IMPROMPTU PERFORMANCE BEGINS
Why do we go hiking?
I have no idea
He's just freestyling.
FREESTYLE RAPPING OVER THE DRUM BEAT
Why do we go hiking?
PUTS THE HIKING STICKS DOWN
TO PICK UP DRUM STICKS
This is fun.
-Car-the needs to come here now.
-Car-the.
YOU'VE BECOME MY WHOLE WORLD
MIMICS CAR, THE GARDEN
WHILE HE'S NOT HERE
THE SONG'S WRITER IS STILL CHECKING IN
"TREE"
ORIGINAL ARTIST: CAR, THE GARDEN
DRUMS: DOWOON
VOCALS: TARZZAN
REACTIONS: LEE CHAE-MIN
A SONG BY A SINGER WHO LOVES NATURE
IT WILL BE SUNG WITHOUT HIM
VOCALS BY TARZZAN
This is amazing.
NOT EVEN HIS SONG
BUT CAN PLAY WITHOUT SHEET MUSIC
THE SONG'S WRITER
IS TOO PREOCCUPIED WITH CHECKING IN
TAKES A ROOM WITH A TREE PAINTING
CAR, THE GARDEN'S SONG
WITHOUT CAR, THE GARDEN
GOING FOR EMOTIONS OVER SKILLS
This song is so difficult to sing.
IT'S EASIER TO EXPRESS WITH HIS BODY
THE CAR, THE GARDEN-LESS PERFORMANCE ENDS
Why isn't Car-the coming?
I'M HERE
AFTER TAKING HIS TIME TUNING THE GUITAR
HIKING: IMPOSSIBLE
SINGING, WRITING LYRICS, COMPOSING,
PLAYING GUITAR AND PIANO: POSSIBLE
HE WANTS TO CAPTURE HIM
DOING HIS DAY JOB
He's so cool.
HE LOOKS COOL EXCEPT WHEN HE'S HIKING
AND SO, THE DAY ENDS
AND THE TIME TO CLIMB UP HALLASAN
COMES CLOSER AND CLOSER
THE MEMBERS ARE GATHERED
IN THE DINING ROOM
I like the vibe here.
Here's the plan for Hallasan
to reach Baengnokdam.
PLANNING THEIR SECOND HIKE
First off, tomorrow,
we'll climb up separately
and meet up at the top.
-That's the goal.
-Right.
WHY DO WE HIKE?
WHY DO WE HIKE SEPARATELY?
Go separately in pairs?
You'll hike in pairs this time.
There are two trails
you can take to Baengnokdam.
2 DIFFERENT TRAILS TO BAENGNOKDAM
BAENGNOKDAM
SEONGPANAK TRAIL, GWANEUMSA TRAIL
I'm sure you got the reservation text.
Since Jung-won and Chae-min
are a bit injured,
we thought…
KNEE INJURY, WRIST INJURY
…the two nursing injuries
should take the Seongpanak trail,
which is a bit easier.
THE SEONGPANAK TRAIL
IS LESS STEEP BUT LONGER
EASY FOR EVEN BEGINNERS TO TRY
SEONGPANAK TRAIL
DIFFICULTY: MODERATE
What was the trail
for the normal people again?
-The Gwaneumsa Trail.
-That's for the normal people?
"Normal people"!
THE GWANEUMSA TRAIL HAS HELLISH STAIRS
THE EXTREME INCLINE TESTS YOUR LIMITS
GWANEUMSA TRAIL
DIFFICULTY: HARD
DESCEND CLUB'S FIRST 2-ON-2 HIKE
We've already decided when to wake up.
-Wake up at 5:20 a.m.
-At 5:20 a.m.
1. WAKE UP AT 5:20 A.M.
Then, what time do we leave from here?
At 6:00 a.m.
2. LEAVE BASE CAMP AT 6:00 A.M.
It'll take about an hour
to get there, right?
We'll drop these two off first.
If we leave at 6:00 a.m.,
will we drop them off at around 6:40 a.m.?
3. GWANEUMSA TEAM ARRIVES AT 6:40 A.M.
Write down, "Drop off at 6:40 a.m."
4. SEONGPANAK TEAM ARRIVES AT 7:00 A.M.
THEN EACH PAIR BEGINS HIKING THEIR TRAIL
So our mission
is just to see Baengnokdam, right?
-Right.
-Just climb up to see it? Okay.
JUST CLIMB UP?
2 RESTRICTIONS ON HIKING HALLASAN
-You have to leave the summit by 1:30 p.m.
-Start climbing down?
FIRST RESTRICTION
THEY MUST ARRIVE AT BAENGNOKDAM
BEFORE 1:30 P.M.
THERE'S ALSO A MYTH ABOUT BAENGNOKDAM…
"ONLY EXTREMELY LUCKY PEOPLE
CAN SEE BAENGNOKDAM"
SECOND RESTRICTION
FICKLE WEATHER AROUND BAENGNOKDAM
THEY NEED TO BE LUCKY WITH THE WEATHER
AND METICULOUSLY CALCULATE HIKING TIME
Then, according to our plan,
we will stay on the summit
for no more than five minutes.
MANAGER CAR IS FIRM
Only five minutes at the top.
I'm telling the crew.
We'll shoot it and climb down right away.
What if we can see Baengnokdam clearly?
What if it's really beautiful?
-Then, let's make it ten minutes.
-Yeah, ten minutes.
Only if there are no clouds.
-If it's cloudy, go right away.
-If so, then five minutes.
-Eight minutes.
-Eight.
COMPROMISING GARDEN
-Meet halfway at eight? Okay.
-Halfway is good.
There's something I want to do.
What is it?
Well,
you and I can make
a big heart in the back,
and you two can make
a small one like this in front.
DOWOON'S ADDITIONAL SUGGESTION
Sure.
-Sure. Like this?
-I want to do that.
But why do you suddenly want to?
-It'll make us look happy.
-Okay, good.
Okay, we'll take a photo of the hearts.
Make it nine minutes.
SHOCKINGLY, HE ACCEPTS THE SUGGESTION
We brought a Polaroid camera.
Do you want it?
Actually, I brought one too.
I brought it just in case I wanted
to capture the moment.
We can use it for our heart photo.
I'll use that then.
-Yes.
-Good.
THINGS TO DO AT SUMMIT FOR 9 MINUTES
1. SEE BAENGNOKDAM
2. GROUP POLAROID PHOTO
Are there any fines to pay?
Is the fine rule still valid?
It is.
He basically pays it regularly.
NEGATIVE COMMENT: 300,000-WON FINE
If you're fined again,
we won't have to pay anything.
Most likely.
HALLASAN HIKING PLAN COMPLETE
Can our audio director check this out?
You don't have to use it
if you don't like it.
USE WHAT?
Really? I see.
A BREAK DURING THE SEORAKSAN HIKE
Are you all right?
My gosh.
This could break your back.
This is madness.
DOWOON WAS SHOCKED BY THE WEIGHT
OF THE AUDIO EQUIPMENT
What is?
Try carrying this.
Are you okay?
DOWOON KEPT WORRYING
ABOUT THE AUDIO DIRECTOR
I ordered something
for our audio director.
-What?
-A walking assist device.
Just wait. I ordered something.
You use it first. Seriously.
HE SENT A WALKING ASSIST DEVICE AS A GIFT
UNBOXING THE GIFT
WALKING ASSIST DEVICE FOR HIKING
REDUCES STRAIN ON LEGS WHILE WALKING
ADJUST THE BELT FIRST
AND STRAP IN THE THIGHS FIRMLY AS WELL
IT GENTLY ASSISTS THE LEGS WHEN WALKING
Is that it?
That's the walking assist device?
Does it help?
But if I use this,
I'll have to carry the battery too.
ADDITIONAL WEIGHT THANKS TO DOWOON
That's one more thing to carry.
Do you walk around like a robot?
-That's right.
-Really?
The motor helps lift the legs.
You're not lifting them?
It's not me.
If you lift a little,
the device lifts it all the way up.
-Like this.
-That's great.
Hear the whirring sound?
THE AUDIO DIRECTOR'S UNBELIEVABLE REVIEW
This is hard to believe.
How is it when climbing stairs?
Like going two steps at a time.
Of course, it helps to climb stairs.
Is it definitely easier?
It is. When climbing up,
it lifts the legs up.
LIFTING HIGH
HIS MOVEMENTS ARE HARD TO BELIEVE
It looks so unnatural.
He's walking like a robot.
AUTOMATICALLY ON ROBOT MODE
You can't stop midway.
Your leg keeps going
until it stops lifting.
Then, you have to walk up like this?
It feels a bit like that.
-It has to go up to here.
-Honestly, this should be enough.
-But like this?
-Yes.
WITH MORE ENERGY
You have to go two at a time.
I'm curious.
Can I try it?
CHAE-MIN TRIES IT HIMSELF
To be honest, I'm thinking
he exaggerated a bit.
I think he was acting.
Do you feel something?
Something suddenly grabbed onto me.
I'll try walking now.
What are you, a robot?
AWKWARD SINCE IT'S HIS FIRST TIME
Try walking naturally.
No, you can't help it.
YOUR LEGS DON'T MOVE THE WAY YOU WANT
HEADS TOWARD THE STAIRS
Is it comfortable?
LIKE A SOLDIER
EVEN MORE AWKWARD
Chae-min, come on.
-He's exaggerating.
-Don't try to be funny.
I'M NOT
Hold on.
IT'S THE SAME WHEN WALKING DOWN AS WELL
CHAE-MIN MOVES MORE AWKWARDLY AS HE GOES
He's acting.
I'm not.
Chae-min, give it to me. Let me try it.
-This is for real!
-Come on.
-How do you stop it?
-It's really like this!
It's really like this. I think…
Hey, tyrant. Nice acting.
FRUSTRATED TYRANT
-You're a good actor.
-No, it's not that.
Do you want to try it?
Seriously, it wasn't on purpose.
-Turn it off first.
-I wasn't trying to be funny.
It feels tight now.
THE ONE WHO PAID FOR IT TRIES
Try lifting your legs.
One by one. Keep going.
-What? So this is what happens.
-What? Come on.
I TOLD YOU
You really do walk like this.
Hold on. But…
Wait. I'll try walking
as if I'm really I'm hiking.
This is good.
Relax and lift your legs,
and they shoot up.
If I lift my legs, it pulls them up.
IF LEGS RELAX
MOVES LIKE A ROBOT
It makes you walk weird.
MY OWN TWO LEGS FEEL UNFAMILIAR
THE SUSPICIOUS CAR-THE TRIES IT ON TOO
KICKING THE AIR
Oh, it's not on yet.
Come on, man.
That was a bit lame.
It was kind of lame, Jung-won.
I'm so disappointed.
EMBARRASSED
I wanted everyone to laugh.
TRYING AGAIN
I can feel it.
Try walking fast.
Okay. It's on?
Lift your legs fast.
LOOKING MORE ENERGETIC
Try the stairs.
The straps came undone.
What the heck? Look at this!
Hey, AI's rebelling!
THE WALKING ASSIST DEVICE
REJECTS ITS NEW OWNER
-It's really moving.
-AI's rebelling.
Hey, what's going on?
THE DEVICE IS HARD TO TAME
You little punk.
Stay still.
Why are you doing this to only me?
Let's work together.
Don't be angry. Okay, let's go.
-Let's go. Hey!
-Try the stairs.
ANOTHER TANTRUM
LOL
This little punk!
PRODUCT REVIEW
IT HATES CAR, THE GARDEN
Stay still. I clearly told you.
A CHAOTIC ENDING
Anyway, thank you so much, Dowoon.
-No worries.
-Seriously.
HE THANKS HIM SINCERELY
It shows how caring Dowoon is.
That's what's important.
This is embarrassing. Let's wash up.
-Thank you, everyone.
-Thank you.
NEXT MORNING
The backpack…
The backpack gets in the way.
UP AND DOWN
SADLY, HE WASN'T ABLE TO WEAR THE DEVICE
Try to adjust the bag.
Let's wash up and go to bed.
-Okay.
-Good job, everyone.
-What's that?
-I bought them in the US.
TARZZAN BRINGS SOMETHING OUT
These are utensils for hiking.
Did you make them?
No, I just saw them
and ordered some for you too.
-Gosh, thank you.
-Sure.
And these are lip balms.
You can each pick one.
CUTE LIP BALMS FROM THE US
CHOCOLATE ENERGY BARS
WITH PACKAGING PERFECT FOR HIKING
A BRAND NEW BACKPACK
-What are you doing?
-What?
-It's my first time trying this bag.
You bought a new one?
Yeah.
SOMEWHAT EMBARRASSED
PACKING TRAIL FOOD ONE BY ONE
FOR TARZZAN
THESE ARE FOR ME
YOON DORAEMON PACKS PLENTY
HE PACKS CUP NOODLES
AND UTENSILS FOR LUNCH AS WELL
THEY FINALLY GO TO BED
We usually have late-night snacks
around this hour.
I know.
Seriously.
EVERYONE GOES TO BED
-Good night.
CURRENT TIME
CHAE-MIN WAKES UP
HE'S THE FIRST TO WAKE UP AS ALWAYS
Did you sleep well?
I slept really well.
-Really?
-Yeah.
DILIGENTLY STARTS HIS MORNING
WITH AN APPLE
Why do I suddenly feel scared?
I have a feeling that it'll be tough.
MEANWHILE, CAR, THE GARDEN
IS ALREADY GETTING DRESSED
Someone's coming down.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
He's already dressed.
HE COMPLAINS BUT GETS READY THE FASTEST
-You slept right away, right?
-Yes.
-I slept so well.
-Right.
-Were you feeling good when we left?
-Yes, I was.
A good night's sleep definitely helped.
It honestly meant one less excuse to make.
LEAVING BASE CAMP
-Let's go.
-Let's check the weather.
Okay. What's with the weather?
What's with the weather? It's not cold.
CURRENT TEMPERATURE: -3°C
WIND SPEED: LIGHT
We won't need padded jackets.
-3°C DOESN'T FEEL COLD FOR THEM NOW
Seat belts, please.
Everyone buckled up?
Let's go.
HEADING FOR HALLASAN
I think there will be
more people on our trail.
-Since it's easier?
-Yeah.
SEONGPANAK TRAIL
DIFFICULTY: MODERATE
Apparently, ours won't be harder
than Seoraksan.
GWANEUMSA TRAIL
DIFFICULTY: HARD
We're here.
We're here. I think you'll start here.
THEY ARRIVE
AT THE GWANEUMSA TRAIL PARKING LOT
THE SUN HASN'T EVEN RISEN YET
THE CAWING OF CROWS
ECHOES THROUGH THE PARKING LOT
ALONG WITH A PERSON'S ROAR
HE BEGINS THE DAY WITH A ROAR
Bye, Chae-min.
Good luck!
-See you later.
-Be safe.
-See you, guys.
-See you.
Bye.
THE CARING DESCEND CLUB
See you at the top.
Good luck.
-Good luck.
-Bye. Be safe.
You too.
CAR, THE GARDEN AND CHAE-MIN
HEAD FOR SEONGPANAK
PUTTING ON CRAMPONS
Did you ever imagine
you and I would take on
a more difficult trail?
A BIT JEALOUS
Next time, I'm coming in injured.
I plan to be hurt next week.
THE TWO WITHOUT INJURIES WILL TAKE
GWANEUMSA TRAIL
THE TRAIL WHERE YOU CAN ENJOY
THE NATURAL SCENERY OF HALLASAN
8.7 KM OF HIKING TO BAENGNOKDAM
HIKING TIME: ABOUT 5 HOURS
AND THEY WILL TAKE
SEONGPANAK TRAIL TO DESCEND
MODERATE SECTION FOR 1 HOUR
HARD SECTION FOR 2 HOURS AND 20 MINUTES
EASY SECTION FOR 20 MINUTES
HARD SECTION FOR 1 HOUR AND 20 MINUTES
THE TRAIL IS NOTORIOUSLY TOUGH
Did you warm up?
Well, we will on the way.
Yeah, on the way.
GWANEUMSA TEAM DEPARTS
It's 7:18 a.m. now.
There's a police officer here.
To prevent illegal activities
or people from going off-trail,
they're stationed here.
I feel so grateful for them.
Hello.
-Hello.
Oh, right. I need to take out my wallet.
THEY ARRIVE AT THE ENTRANCE
ONLY 500 PEOPLE A DAY CAN ENTER
GWANEUMSA WITH RESERVATIONS
Here it is.
1. SHOW ID
Show me the QR code as well.
2. SHOW QR CODE
You may enter.
-Thank you.
-Have a nice day.
THEY PASS THROUGH THE ENTRANCE
I feel hot.
There sure is a temperature difference.
CURRENTLY -2.9°C
IT FEELS RELATIVELY WARM
HIKING AS A PAIR FOR THE FIRST TIME
FLAT IN THE BEGINNING
LEAD: TARZZAN
TAIL: DOWOON
IN FORMATION AS A PAIR TOO
It's quite rocky here too.
It's actually basalt here.
You're right.
SINCE THE MOUNTAIN WAS FORMED
BY VOLCANIC ERUPTIONS
BASALT IS EVERYWHERE
This is a rocky mountain too.
THERE ARE A LOT OF ROCKS
SO HE'S NOT WRONG
It's a volcano.
Right, it's a volcano.
It was fun to see basalt.
It was everywhere on the ground
since it was a volcano.
That was…
It was… fun.
LAUGHING
LOOKING AROUND
What's this?
SURROUNDING THE TRAIL
THIS IS…
It's bamboo.
Bamboo?
-It's bamboo.
-Bamboo? Really?
They're broadleaf bamboo.
They're called joritdae.
DWARF SPECIES OF BAMBOO
You'll see them everywhere
while hiking Hallasan.
Isn't the scenery here
totally different from the others?
Totally.
TARZZAN ENJOYS THE SCENERY
AND THE DOCENT ENJOYS EXPLAINING
This says "Gwaneumsa 5-1," right?
-Yes.
It means Gwaneumsa
is the fifth trail on Hallasan,
and this number changes every 250 m.
This "one" means we've come 250 m.
If you see "5-34,"
you're on the summit.
You can tell
how much you've climbed from that.
Okay. So, each number is 250 m.
JUST WHEN IT SEEMED THEY WERE GOING…
Right, this spot.
There's something I should explain to you.
ANOTHER AREA FOR THE DOCENT TO EXPLAIN
It's called "Guringul Cave."
A LAVA CAVE FORMED
BY AN ERUPTION FROM BAENGNOKDAM
It's the highest lava cave in Korea.
700 M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
Hikers are not allowed to go in.
Only cultural heritage experts
are allowed.
Let's go.
ALLERGIC TO DOCENTS
SETTING OFF AGAIN
Let's just check out
the map of the trail here.
HE FOUND THE TRAIL MAP
From the Tamna Valley Bridge,
for about two and a half hours,
it's a hard section.
What about the other trail?
Is it easy all the way through for them?
It's easy overall,
but there's a hard part at the end.
Let's go. We shouldn't overthink it.
It's doable so far, Dowoon.
TODAY'S GWANEUMSA TRAIL IS…
SNOWY AND STEEP
LEG FATIGUE BUILDS UP
IT'S GOING TO BE A TOUGH HIKE
MEANWHILE,
CAR, THE GARDEN AND CHAE-MIN
-Thanks.
-Sure.
SEONGPANAK TEAM ARRIVES
20 MINUTES AFTER THE OTHER TEAM
CHECKING OUT THE MOUNTAIN
CURRENTLY -0.3°C,
IT IS CERTAINLY WARMER THAN LAST HIKE
NODDING
TAKING THEIR BACKPACKS
We don't need crampons?
Are we putting on crampons?
LET'S PUT THEM ON
DENIED SINCE HE'S NOT A BUS
BUSES ONLY
I was checking if it moved.
-Does it move a lot?
-It does.
That's a bad start for today.
HE ENDS UP PUTTING THEM ON WHILE SITTING
What?
What's wrong?
The buckle's gone.
THE WAIST BUCKLE'S GONE
I guess I'm given a handicap
since the trail's easier.
IT'S TIME TO WARM UP NOW
People might think
we're climbing the Himalayas.
Are you trying to stall?
-I'm just warming up thoroughly.
-I see.
A LOT OF FUSS WARMING UP FOR AN EASY TRAIL
I was just wondering.
-Let's go, Chae-min.
-Let's go.
SEONGPANAK TEAM DEPARTS
AN ENERGETIC START UNLIKE OTHER TIMES
-It definitely feels less cold.
-Right.
It's not bad.
THEY ARRIVE AT THE TRAIL ENTRANCE
It feels pretty different
from the other mountains.
The signs also look expensive…
-What do you mean?
-They look expensive.
You know what I mean.
Well, I'd say
the information boards are bigger.
Shouldn't we see our route
while we're here?
Sounds good.
SEONGPANAK TRAIL
THANKS TO ITS GENTLE INCLINE
AND WELL-ORGANIZED PATH
IT'S THE MOST POPULAR TRAIL
AMONG ALL HIKERS
EASY SECTION FOR 1 HOUR AND 40 MINUTES
MODERATE SECTION FOR 1 HOUR AND 20 MINUTES
HARD SECTION FOR 1 HOUR AND 30 MINUTES
It takes four and a half hours.
9.6 KM OF HIKING TO BAENGNOKDAM
AND THEY WILL TAKE
THE SAME ROUTE TO DESCEND
The other guys are climbing up from there.
Ours is definitely much longer.
-Yeah, ours is longer.
-It is.
The incline's apparently gentle,
so let's go.
Simple?
-Gentle.
-I see.
Gosh, I'm so mad
that this buckle's gone.
I should get a new K2 backpack.
Good thinking.
I'll buy new clothes
from K2 next time too.
Good idea.
ONLY 1,000 PEOPLE A DAY CAN ENTER
SEONGPANAK WITH RESERVATIONS
SEONGPANAK BEGINS
WITH WOODEN STEPS ON A GENTLE INCLINE
It's a breeze so far.
If only it can be like this until the end.
Seriously.
If it was, it'd be nice for everyone,
including our camera operators.
-Right.
-It'd be great for everyone.
PRODUCER NAH SIGHS
What?
Overall, Producer Nah
is a pretty slow hiker.
Should we match his pace?
Yeah, let's go at this pace.
I can't go faster. And Chae-min…
His strides are so long.
He's insane.
When we hiked Seoraksan, he wasn't tired.
If we keep pace with him, we'll be toast.
And you know, right?
This Seongpanak trail
is only full of the old and the weak.
This trail? Really?
-I'm "old."
-Good.
-And I'm "weak."
"Weak."
It's "old," "weak," and "person."
OLD NAH, WEAK CAR, CHAEMIN THE PERSON
let's take it slow.
Still, our producer Hyun-yong
isn't here with us,
-we don't have to stop and listen to him.
-I love it.
If he were here,
he'd be explaining what these were.
THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT HE'S DOING ON GWANEUMSA
I bet Dowoon will be awfully quiet today.
THE OLD AND WEAK
SUDDENLY WORRY ABOUT THE OTHERS
Dowoon's not feeling well today?
It's not that.
He just doesn't talk much while hiking.
Maybe he wants to hide his fake dialect.
When he's really exhausted…
He talks in a Seoul accent.
He's probably very confused
since it's all mixed up.
YAWNING
GWANEUMSA TEAM HAS CLIMBED 2.5 KM
THEY ARE STILL ON THE MODERATE SECTION
I'm starting to feel it.
-Right?
-Yeah.
Thank goodness.
STEPS GOING DOWN APPEAR
After all that climbing,
why are we going down again?
Right?
"HIKING" IS ALL ABOUT CLIMBING UP
Damn.
IF THERE'S A PATH GOING DOWN
That must be the "Stairway to Heaven."
THERE'S ANOTHER GOING UP
"TO GO UP, ONE NEEDS COURAGE TO GO DOWN."
-NIETZSCHE
Now, it's difficult.
THE HARD SECTION BEGINS
THE STAFF'S PICK
1ST CRUX
These stairs are insane.
-Should we let them pass?
-Yeah, we should.
GIVING WAY FOR NO REASON
INTIMIDATED
THE END OF THE STAIRS IS BARELY VISIBLE
Let's go.
THEY START CLIMBING
BARELY ENOUGH ROOM
FOR A SINGLE FOOT ON THE NARROW STEPS
This is dangerous. Let's be careful.
-Geez.
-Goodness.
FROM TARZZAN'S CAM
CLIMBING USING BOTH STICKS
FROM DOWOON'S CAM
We should hold on to the ropes.
It's dangerous.
HOLDING ON TO THE ROPE WITH ONE HAND
FROM TARZZAN'S CAM
BUT THE ROPE IS NOT TAUT ENOUGH
The sticks weren't enough,
so we had to hold the ropes.
But the ropes were so loose.
They were limp.
LEFT HAND, HIKING STICK
RIGHT HAND, ROPE
HARD TO EVEN KEEP THEIR BALANCE
A PERSON AHEAD OF THEM
IS ALSO HOLDING ON TO THE ROPE
NOT ABLE TO PICK UP THE PACE
DEEP SIGH
THEY ARE HALFWAY THROUGH
GROANS
Geez.
Jung-won should be here.
Right?
THEY MUST KEEP GOING UP
THEY KEEP GOING WITHOUT A BREAK
SWAYS
FROM TARZZAN'S CAM
Geez, it's even steeper here.
VERY STEEP
I felt like I'd slip and fall if I rested,
so I had to keep going.
GOING MAD
TARZZAN ARRIVES
DOWOON ARRIVES SOON AFTER
I feel like there's less oxygen here.
We climbed so high.
SO STEEP
Whoever said Hallasan was flat…
Seriously…
It was good in the beginning.
I thought, "If we keep going like this,
it'll be doable."
But then, I slowly got angry
once the stairs started.
We're at 5-12 now.
After all that climbing?
It's a third of the way.
THEY'VE COME 3 KM BUT…
We're just now at the welcome sign.
SORRY FOR THE LATE GREETINGS
I'm so pissed off.
There it is.
Let's go take a break.
THE FIRST REST AREA IS IN SIGHT
1 HOUR AND 17 MINUTES PASSED
THEY ARRIVE AT TAMNA VALLEY RESTROOM
DAZED
I should've borrowed
those robot legs from last night.
-I think they'd be helpful.
-They'd really help with step.
THE OWNER OF THE WALKING ASSIST DEVICE
HYDRATING HIMSELF QUICKLY
God, that's nice.
Want some water?
-No, you drink it. I have some.
-Okay.
THEY REFUEL WITH SNACKS NEXT
A BITE OF THE SNACKS
HE BROUGHT FROM THE US
Give me the trash.
No, I'm going to eat it little by little.
THREE CAWS
They say a crow cawing three times
means bad luck.
Caw, caw, caw.
WILL THEY BE ABLE TO SEE
BAENGNOKDAM TODAY?
They say you need three generations
of luck to get such nice weather to see.
What do you think, Dowoon?
I hope my son will get to see it.
PASSING DOWN THE RIGHT TO SEE BAENGNOKDAM
NODDING
Without Jung-won here,
I've become the grumpy one.
DOWOON, THE GARDEN
Let's go.
But you didn't lower our morale,
so that shouldn't be a fine.
I agree.
In fact, it boosted our morale.
PRESIDENT TAR APPROVES
CAW, CAW
That's so annoying.
IT BOTHERS HIM
THEY LEAVE TAMNA VALLEY RESTROOM
Seriously, Jung-won should've come here.
-He missed out on this amazing scenery.
-Right.
What a shame.
MEANWHILE, THE SEONGPANAK TEAM…
THEY STILL LOOK LIVELY
THEIR FIRST INFORMATION BOARD APPEARS
What's the difficulty color here?
YOU ARE HERE
EASY
The red section will be hard.
What's with the difficult one?
It continues until the end.
-Right.
-Isn't this supposed to be easy?
-You came here thinking it'd be easy.
-This trail's much easier.
This is different from what I'd heard.
-Hello.
-This man's famous.
Hi. How old are you?
I'm in the seventh grade.
SUDDENLY TALKING
WITH A SEVENTH GRADER AND HIS MOTHER
Do you know who that hairy guy is?
Do you know me? Have you seen me before?
-I don't know.
-You don't?
That's good.
He doesn't watch YouTube much.
He's right. You shouldn't know me.
My young friend, why do you hike?
Because my mom made me go.
That's hilarious.
It's because of his mom.
Then, you didn't want to come?
THE MOTHER IS FLUSTERED
Me too. This guy dragged me here.
You know he does that a lot.
I was totally duped.
TWO PEOPLE WHO DRAGGED OTHERS HERE
Are you going up to the top?
Yeah. What about you?
I'm going too.
To the top? To be honest, I don't want to.
Dae-seong, let's go ahead.
Good luck on your hike.
Thank you. Take care.
FEELING THE NEGATIVE VIBE,
THEY GO ON AHEAD
We finally got our first answer at least.
-"My mom made me go."
WHY ON EARTH DO YOU HIKE?
MY MOM MADE ME GO
If you're a seventh grader…
you don't even join
your family to go eat out.
-True.
-But he came to Hallasan?
It means he's a good son.
Of course, he is.
A mom brought her son here.
That means
this trail isn't that hard.
-Right?
-Right.
ANOTHER THING THAT PROVES
THIS ISN'T A DIFFICULT TRAIL
A HIKER IN CASUAL CLOTHING
A true hiker.
What? Who is that?
I'M A HIKER
NEWSBOY CAP, CASHMERE COAT,
JEANS, UGG BOOTS
That's so stylish.
There were many people hiking casually.
There was even someone
hiking in jeans and a coat.
They just had some light crampons
on their shoes.
I thought maybe we were
making a fuss with our outfits.
Gosh, hiking in a coat…
This makes our outfits embarrassing.
Right. Hiking in Uggs is amazing.
-We're 800 m high now?
-Yeah.
PASSING 800 M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
This is nice!
It is.
Doesn't it still feel
like a walking trail today?
Yeah.
Yeah, let's go like this
for another hour.
To be honest, I liked it.
In the beginning,
it felt like we went up pleasantly.
The area we walked was almost flat.
It felt like a warm-up.
Thanks to the easy section,
we were able to warm up enough.
MAYBE CHAE-MIN IS TOO WARMED UP
WIPING SWEAT AWAY
It sure is hot today.
I might end up
taking off all my layers today.
It's hot.
UNZIPS JACKET
TAKING OFF GLOVES
ADJUSTING LAYERS
DRYING SWEAT
UNZIPS HIS INNER LAYER AS WELL
Hold on.
Could you remove the mic?
I want to take this off.
BREAK TIME TO ADJUST CLOTHES
I'm sweating so much.
-You'll wear only one layer?
-Yes, I'm so hot now.
What? Do you like undressing in public?
-Just one layer?
-Yes.
I feel so hot.
My whole back is drenched.
A VIGOROUS GUY
Gosh, he's so unpredictable.
You're pretty passionate.
Yes, that's how I usually am.
He's a passionate guy.
See the sweat here?
-Yeah.
-You really are sweating.
Yes.
I'm really hot right now.
It wasn't that the trail was hard.
It was really… It was just hot.
I was sweating more than the others,
but I think most of us
did sweat a lot too.
It wasn't that hot,
but he took his clothes off.
Since he's a model,
I thought some ad sponsor
asked him to do it.
WHOOSH
And with the sweat…
WIPING SWEAT AWAY
He keeps staring off somewhere.
I guess it was a good idea.
It wasn't my plan.
But I got to show off
every layer of my outfit naturally.
CURRENT LOCATION
It's a cedar forest.
-Cider?
-"Cedar."
I see.
A DENSE FOREST OF CEDARS
THAT ARE GREEN ALL YEAR ROUND
WITH A GREEN AND FLAT TRAIL INSIDE
I hear it emits a lot of phytoncides.
A FOREST TRAIL FULL OF PHYTONCIDES
INHALING RIGHT AWAY
-This is all right.
-It's nice.
It's beautiful here.
Yeah, it's pretty nice here.
CAPTURING THE SCENERY WITH HIS FILM CAMERA
Gosh, this mountain is really nice.
EVEN CAR, THE GARDEN LIKES THE SCENERY
It's so beautiful here.
But the thing is,
this is still the easiest section.
-But isn't it so beautiful?
-It is.
It's okay so far.
I wonder if they're having a tough time.
Honestly, this trail's not bad. Right?
-Right.
-I feel bad.
WORRYING ABOUT THE GWANEUMSA TEAM
The trees are all cedars now.
THE GWANEUMSA TEAM
IS ALSO LOOKING AT THE CEDARS
It definitely smells different now.
I smell something.
These cedars emit a lot of phytoncides.
You smell it too, right?
I do. But it just smells like trees.
That was beautiful.
Suddenly, in the middle section…
The really tall ones were cedars, right?
The cedar forest was the most memorable.
I think those are animal footprints.
You're right.
-They're definitely not a human's.
-You're right.
Maybe a deer's?
Right?
That definitely can't be a human's.
DISCOVERS SOMETHING
I think this was a boar,
judging by the shape.
BOAR FOOTPRINTS?
FOOTPRINTS OUTSIDE THE TRAIL
THE SHAPES
AND DIRECTIONS ARE ALL DIFFERENT
It passed through here.
-Some look like a cat's.
-Right.
Hey, someone wrote my name there.
-Who?
-Over here.
Isn't it "Jae-won"?
I should change it.
ADDS A STROKE
MR. LEE CHAE-WON IS SATISFIED
Was it written as "Dowoon"?
Yes, over there.
DOWOON
"Dowoon"?
Gosh, who was it?
You should've told me.
IT MAKES HIM HAPPY
This is fun.
It's fun seeing these.
I guess many people
write their names here.
Like a guest book, you know?
Right.
It's romantic.
I WAS HERE
LEE DONG-SEOP
JIN-GYU
HYEON
I liked that too.
There was snow around the trail.
And some people wrote
messages in the snow.
It was kind of like
a guest book for the trail.
I thought that was pretty romantic.
-Should we write something too?
-We should.
"Tarzzan was here."
I'll write your name big.
DOWOON AND TARZZAN WERE HERE
It's cute.
Put your handprint too.
THE TWO OF THEM WERE HAVING A NICE TIME
If you sit, you and the message
will be in frame.
THE DOCENT WANTED A PHOTO
I need you to sit to get a good angle.
Good. Looks great.
One, two, three. Look here.
We shouldn't write again.
We learned a lesson.
Yeah, we did.
It says, "Don't come here."
"Don't come here."
DON'T COME HERE
A WARNING FROM SOMEONE
THE PATH AHEAD OF THEM
IS STILL A LONG WAY TO GO
THEY CLIMB
Gosh, my calves are about to explode.
This part is tough too.
AND CLIMB AGAIN
As soon as I saw it,
I knew it'd be really tough.
Honestly, it was ridiculous.
THE STEPS OF GWANEUMSA TRAIL
GO ON ENDLESSLY
Seriously, it was killing me.
I thought my legs were going to give out.
-Wait, Dowoon.
-What?
I have no idea how that happened.
I still don't remember.
DON'T COME HERE
I'm just not coming back again.
Hallasan?
I'm never coming back.
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu